Newman, Harold Selected Correspondence 6191
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Harold Newman Selected Correspondence
1977-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Newman, Harold R.
6191
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Papers, correspondence.
8399867
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 13, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Newman, Harold
8399867
- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  July 1977. Regarding possible appointment as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board.
- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  August 1977. Recommendation for appointment as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board
- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  October 1977 Councilgram. Congratulations to Newman on his appoint as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board.
- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  November 1977. Mostly ongratulations to Newman on his appoint as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board and his responses.
- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  December 1977. Mostly congratulations to Newman on his appoint as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board and his responses.
- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  January 1978. Mostly ongratulations to Newman on his appoint as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board and his responses.
- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  February 1978. Mostly congratulations to Newman on his appoint as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board and his responses.
- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  March 1978. Mostly congratulations to Newman on his appoint as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board and his responses.
- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  April 1978. Mostly congratulations to Newman on his appoint as Chairman of the New York State Public Employees Relations Board and his responses.
- Correspondence, 1988-1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  April 1988. Regarding David Randles' appointment as the New York Member of the Port Authority Labor Relations Panel. Includes an explanatory note from January 1998.
- Retirement, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Includes letters of congratulations, news clippings, program, and other materials